Hello friends, the channel heartily welcomes you to the
life insurance company
and if we talk about the results, they have been excellent
and the quarterly results are
very good results, however, the
early results are also there and if we talk about the
open date, it has been quite good today
and if we talk about one month, then even now the
stock is
down by 8% in one month and this group, the
entire Nifty is down in this month, the entire market is down,
so due to this the stock is also going down right now,
if we talk about it, there is a little thing in the stock even in 6 months,
if we talk about the
stock even in this year,
but this is an excellent company in the insurance sector
and if we look after HDFC
and in the maximum time, this company has
generated good returns and if we
look at the maximum, till now its investment can be
said to be 65%, if we talk about the stock then it becomes
HDFC Life
because HDFC Life
is also a leader in its sector,
so let us talk about
ICICI Prudential, the
graph of both is
about
6 months  If we look at it, there is a
growth of about one and a half percent in HDFC.
HDFC is down by 24% and 18% right now. If we
look at the situation further, for five years, the
situation
changes completely in 5 years and Dhoni, who is a lion,
ICICI is up 5% in 5 years,
he always
studies it
and if we look at it, then it will be available first
and the one who fills the cream, if we look at it according to 45% face
value, then you have been given a
difference of 45% in it and this is the last
date
and this is its record date,
so let's say the
statement result
premium is given, so the grow
premium is 450
[music]
lakh in it and if we
talk about question number, in the quarter it has become 500
and the quarterly growth is very slight,
if we talk about the total, it has become
397 and if we talk about September, it has become 450,
so if we look at it, there is year to year
growth in it and if we look at their quarterly, then the
total expenses of the company are also there in it, so if we talk about the total expenses, then let's go to the
total of the company.  If there is expenditure then the
total is expensive, the total has been
reduced and similarly if we look at the
balance sheet of insurance companies, banks and insurance companies, then if we look at it, the most
important thing is that the company does
not have any company, at
present the company does not have any money
and if we look from here then the company will be
in a strong position, and if we
look at the result of the company, it is
year down, the
growth in the result of the company and in this quarter the
NPA of the company is also not at all,
NPA is exactly in this quarter and the
company also has a lot of losses in this quarter
and from running and the
premium that the company gets as insurance is quite high
and if someone adds up then there is growth in the income of the company
and if we look at the net income of the company, then in the
income of the company, the
payment of the company is about 13%, if we
look at the result of the company,
subscribe to the company quadratically and press the bell icon and
then select all so that the
new video is in the next video, thank you